Narrator: 1
Max: Hey, Lucy. I’m trying to study, and you’re making too much noise.
Lucy: It isn’t noise, it’s Beethoven. I’m practicing – I have a school concert tomorrow.
You can study downstairs.
Max: I can’t, Jake’s playing a video game.
Lucy: What about the kitchen?
Max: No, Dad’s cooking dinner, and he’s listening to a soccer game.
It’s impossible to work in this house!
Narrator: 2
Paul: Isabel! Can you come here?
Isabel: What’s the matter?
Paul: What’s happening next door?
Why’s their dog barking? I can’t hear the radio.
Isabel: They’re having a party in their yard.
Paul: Not again! Can you go and talk to them?
Isabel: Yes, good idea. It’s their second party in three weeks!